I could get used to
[music]
your [music]
used
night.
Good evening.
Time check. It's 7:49
p.m. Yes. And kaka sunset lang or yan
malwa pa pil palang yam. And I'm using a
mic like
[music] and we need that. And we are
cooking kimchi jig today. That's our
dinner
cuz I like it that way. But can we all
just appreciate
look at the sky? Actually
vlog
sunset the past few days. I'm going to
pop
a sunset ganda.
Guys, lately we have different sunset
views in this apartment and I'm just so
happy that we renewed our stay here.
Anyway,
salt and pepper.
But I have here
salt.
vlog sunset. Look at that. It's so
beautiful, guys.
These are the moments. Thankful
ganda.
The store official kimchi.
Let's do it. [music]
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay, let's add some water
and then simmer.
to
ta.
[music]
Yum.
>> [laughter]
>> Hello.
Up up up to here.
Up up up up up up up up up up up up up
up up up up up up up up here. Up
up up up up up up up up up up up up up
up up up up up up up.
Say hi.
Say hi vlog. Hi vlog. I'm Sandy.
Sandy, this is not for you.
No,
we are finally doing a kitchen makeover.
Actually, an apartment makeover. And
palang episode one cuz we're going to
start with kitchen and then you know
walk-in vanity area and then of course
sofa and stuffing.
I only have like two weeks left before I
start [screaming]
my school. I'm so excited guys. I'm
going to take you to my first day of
classes and
going to be busy cuz
every day classes.
ion. Anyway,
let's eat. And tomorrow we go to a house
fair. Coex ulit. If last vlog, if you've
watched our last vlog, stationary fair,
more on art fair and stuff. This time
around, it's going to be all about home,
home essentials, kitchen and stuff. So
excited. Super excited. And lang. So
that's it. Cheers to our ano makeover
series.
Share. Good morning.
I'm playing between my two cameras.
Let me know if you want this camera or
this camera. I'm ready to leave in a few
minutes. But we're going to have some
breakfast. And guys, it's so hard to
keep drinking water if it's so hot. I'm
always craving for a drink that has a
really good taste. So, I have a lot of
coconut water.
coconut water. I also tried Power Itid,
but lately this is my favorite. I bought
this last April, March maybe when we
went to the 12th grocery store and ever
since then I've been drinking it and na.
Anyway, this drink guys, it's low in
sugar. It tastes really refreshing and
it's basically my beauty drink as well.
So, I just add some water guys. Yeah.
Lang mog water and then you mix it.
Basically guys, it's a drink that
supports not only the glow from your
skin but also s hair. If you notice,
look at that. And look at my nails guys.
I think this is the healthiest version
of my nails.
Cuz this drink guys has biotin. So very
important for nail and hair growth.
Biotin talaga. So to me biotin, vitamin
C, B3, B6, hyaluronic acid, collagen
peptides and more in this drink.
Actually glutathion is also in this
drink. And just like that, we have the
drink. I just put the ice mga kalahhat
and trust me s breakfast is served. We
have her drink and pancake
before he [music] left for school.
Anyway, I'm eating here cuz I still have
some work to do before we leave. So,
kangi. Anyway, let's eat.
Super duper sy like 10 out of 10.
Refreshing. And this is it. By the way,
guys, when taking glutathione, the most
important thing to look out for is the
purity and glutathione content. So guys,
with 90% high purity glutathion, I can
really feel my [music] skin getting
brighter and healthier, less effort when
it comes to prepping my skin with
makeup. Sometimes I don't need concealer
anymore. Something like that. And
ingredients very very important.
This one has a lot of powerful
antioxidant that helps with fine lines
and wrinkles. So very nice din talaga na
drink aside from the fact so naman. Also
today's agenda like I've mentioned last
night we're heading to the fair 10:00
a.m. slot. So I'm going to head out. I
think 40 to 1 hour to go there via train
malay gang nam sin. So I'm going to
finish some work and then we're going to
head out.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Hey,
ha.
>> [music]
[music]
>> my uniform. White polo, [laughter]
white shorts, white everything. White,
white shoes.
We are in coex again.
Hopefully
I think in a few weeks time me nam
coffee fair and whatever ano ba. So
let's go guys. Okay I booked my tickets
via the neighbor app per naman the walk
in. Okay here it is.
Okay compared to the illustration fair.
Madam and they gave us a welcome gift
shopping bag. Thankful
and guys.
Oh my god. OMG. OMG. Binaga namaga
masag. Oh matcha ba for this.
I don't know where to start. Wait for
the cats.
Bed for the cats.
[music] Nina
sa dami nakita to nice diniwan manip na
lang si guys. Oh I think these are hand
painted. Oh they have a studio. Oh meron
sa Malaysia Hong Kong. Oh meron Manila
guys. It's me Manila
guys when we were living in the
Philippines parang ano parang shelves
may kitchen brand it's [music] called
rare rose in order here Korea first time
seeing them
pala
so nice
tissue
very sleek
bigger
I'm not sure
blue
guys plant store
very cute
guys. Let's research first compa.
We have this one as well. Indoor garden
guys para angry.
I really like this so far. We'll come
back.
Found the top store that I want to
visit.
I hope they sell
I've been wanting this guys. Please
don't judge me. I cover railings.
So,
guys, I think we need some of these for
our meal prep. Mix and match pala guys
like
set up. actually pa lunchbox
meal prep if you want kimchi ganyan
lunch
store. So I got a fabric or an art from
them
guys actual like drawing
cute art
shelves
athetic.
This one nam man guys custom clock
depend colorway and stuff. Cool. These
are really nice. Actually guys if you
remember [music] this artist
illustration pair thinking about buying
this cute
or this one lunch cuz it's giving
restaurant
cute brush.
Oh this is nice.
Guys, I'm picking between the two.
[music]
guys. Look, they have some book covers.
This is really nice.
Oh, wow.
store
shapes [gasps]
you can expect.
So
bowl and stuff lamp and those are all
portable
>> here and
>> it's wireless guys. Yes, we have a three
level of dimming.
>> It's so nice.
>> Yes. So beautiful.
This is really beautiful guys in
personality
tray. Honestly,
portableity
and I think original design. Do I need
another coaster?
bowl
aesthetic home. Look at this store. It's
so cute.
We should get this one. It's sandy.
Cute.
Well, let's check pala mga plants.
I pa yung lamp ano eto ba yan this one I
think I [music] just found the perfect
plan for our kitchen
guys
I'm [music] a huge fan of this artist I
can't believe anganda in person
wow [music]
grab it to see this in actual I'm ga
guys. I'm going.
[music]
Okay guys, we're done with the fair
plant and then also got a plate and then
artsy pieces.
quite disappointed
more on both plates and
stationary
stores
like maps in hope
and stuff and
so we can drop this off and then we'll
see maybe we can go to Yongan later
or so let's go well let's check Zara
home and narin t Literal pagalas ng coax
zara home. Here it is.
Anyway guys, let's go home. 40 to 50
minutes away apartment here. So it's
going to be a long ride. Just got home.
Say hi to the vlog. Say hi. Hello guys.
Finally,
our orders have arrived. As mentioned,
guys, I got some organizers and
dispensers for our kitchen. And this is
just the first part.
Home
like last time
home.
Anyway, finally. So, I got these shelves
organizing.
I'll show you guys later. I got four of
these.
Going to link it below, guys.
Most of the time rocket coupon
before 12 midnight.
In fairness, it's affordable. 14,1
in order
salt, pepper and stuff,
okay naman pero
too big
toy though
Mars it's giving
jogging maga too big but maganda naman
naang. Anyway, let's do this. Let's
start. Wait,
guys. Please don't judge me. Okay.
I have my narr
allpurpose flour
till now
guys. Last time
oil and vinegar. Anyway, it is what it
is.
Shelf. Let's start.
[music]
Waiting for the brightest
[singing]
[music]
perch. Okay.
At least an Okay guys. So finally this
is how it looks.
So far I'm happy. Okay naman
segregation. Honestly guys I like it. I
feel like organized in a way
and also like olive oil.
Anyway, let's start organizing together.
Okay, let's start here. Going to put my
supplements
over here
and also this one. This one recent
purchase from the grocery.
I'm still consistent with my apple
cider. [music] So on hand and then last
my collagen box
that very nice here
powdered milk
cooking wine and then marine soy sauce
for adobo. Surprise surprise.
We're here in Hongi station. We're
meeting someone special and we're taking
them to one of my favorite places
and so going to take them there because
it's shock
and
she's a booker. I'm a boogieist.
[laughter]
I'm a boogieist.
50 pages.
So, I'm reading a book called Science by
Laura Jean.
>> And S science, huh? S I G N S. Science
as in science. She's a psychic medium,
which means she can talk to the dead.
She's like teaching us how to
communicate with the people on the other
side. There's no such thing as
coincidences.
When you say coincidence, oh my gosh,
sign.
It's not a coincidence. It's supposed to
happen to you. It's supposed to happen.
[music]
>> [music]
>> right here.
[music]
Shinhong Art Market so they can explore
a bit while we go to the Shinon shop. So
plates, bowls and stuff. Cafe lang d
sila sagit. We're here.
Oh my [music] god. Ang ganda. Wow.
This is so nice.
Oh love.
[music]
It's really cute.
>> It's [music] quite heavy.
So cute.
Yes.
Oh, 62,0001.
That's really nice. It's made in Italy.
This is giving inflatable pool. Oh, made
in Germany
to mga to
gando. Look at this. It's so cute.
Actually nice to naman blue.
Super. Yes. Wow. Anganda anganda design.
Look,
look at that. The stars
and this one sun.
Parang nice to for me guys.
This one is bigger para nong rice board.
I really like it.
You need to do
it just
[music]
checking this out, guys. I've always
wanted this one. Parang ganong size
[music] talagay nin dun sa may sofa
area.
[music]
Life update. We're here in Yoidong Hang
Park. This is one of the most famous Han
River spots
like around 500
river.
So I think this is the perfect time. Ta
spider gum mag spider web [laughter]
ano naman
as in
>> getting ready for bed
[laughter]
bro catch up bro
hey mag relax
under the
>> [music]
>> We got time [singing]
on our side.
We're in a state of home. I [music] need
you [singing]
my thought.
I want you to know that every
[music and singing] time you're away,
I long for you so much. I can find my
way.
[music]
Next goal.
Yellow table
[music and singing]
makes it all
>> sound on.
[singing and music]
Do you feel we got something wrong?
[music]
And I saw [singing] you
walk in the light. [music]
And the [singing] truth may come as a
surprise
that we are feel. [singing and music]
So, we're going to walk from the Han
River to their hotel and my apartment.
So, and this is the Han River.
[laughter]
I
>> Good morning. Time for our morning walk
with Sandy. But just a quick life
update.
to my apartment. Total steps last night
20k steps guys
apartment.
I had so much fun, nice conversation,
nice company.
It's just that
kitchen and stuff. So after we walk
Sandy, which brings me to figure out
I like it because you can customize the
color of the bottle and then handle and
then this one. It's really nice.
Perfect. You can sip here and then um
straw naman here
which is
glowin drink the beauty drink one. I'll
link it in the description box.
I'm planning to bring Sandy Park and
usually walk like 1 hour
today
park
for dogs
environment.
Also, it's an excuse for me to read a
few chapters of a new book, guys.
Recent read, which is Fort W.
I like fantasy. When I was in high
school, I remember loving the Mortal
Instrument series, Shadow Hunters and
stuff,
Heavenly Fire
getting back to fantasy.
So, I don't know.
I like it. I just thought it's
an Harry Potter Hunger Games and then
sprinkle League of Legends concept
anyway
and then let's go.
I'll do this later after
[music and singing]
>> [music]
[singing]
>> M
[music]
I need more.
[singing]
>> [music]
>> Don't show me [singing and music]
[music and singing]
so far.
Anyway, more in the coming vlogs. Let me
know if you have any suggestions,
comments.
But I
I'm not so sure.
[singing and music]
>> [music]